[{"instructions":"Let's define a new operation +<sub>6</sub>. This operation will give us a way of combining two of the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 to get another one of them back. To perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. (That's why the operation is called +<sub>6</sub>.) <br /><br />For example, 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2, because 3 + 5 = 8, and 8 is bigger than 6, so we subtract 6, and 8 - 6 = 2. So 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2.<br /><br />Similarly, 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5, because 1 + 4 = 5, and 5 is less than 6 so we leave it alone.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":56360,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":1,"time_elapsed":1379168,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Do you see how +<sub>6</sub> works? By subtracting 6 every time we get above 5, we ensure t hat when  we combine two numbers using +<sub>6</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 5.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":21214,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":2,"time_elapsed":1400383,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now try one on your own! What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":7966,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":3,"time_elapsed":1408350,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 3 because 4 + 5 = 9 and 9 - 6 = 3.","rt":1563,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":4,"time_elapsed":1409914,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":5732,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":5,"time_elapsed":1415646,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 5 because 3 + 2 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1518,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":6,"time_elapsed":1417166,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to ge t your r esult.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":6464,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":7,"time_elapsed":1423630,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0 because 1 + 5 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":3151,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":8,"time_elapsed":1426782,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":4822,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":9,"time_elapsed":1431605,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Co rrect! 1  +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 2 because 1 + 1 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":1168,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":10,"time_elapsed":1432774,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":4399,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":11,"time_elapsed":1437174,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 3 because 3 + 0 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":1047,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":12,"time_elapsed":1438222,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<s ub>6</su b>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":3904,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":13,"time_elapsed":1442126,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 2 because 4 + 4 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":1112,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":14,"time_elapsed":1443238,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":19222,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":15,"time_elapsed":1462461,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 4 because 1 + 3 = 4 and 4 is less than 6.","rt":1152,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":16,"time_elapsed":1463614,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":5095,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":17,"time_elapsed":1468710,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 1 because 4 + 3 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1111,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":18,"time_elapsed":1469822,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":3438,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":19,"time_elapsed":1473261,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 5 because 0 + 5 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1031,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":20,"time_elapsed":1474293,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's you r result . If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":4560,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":21,"time_elapsed":1478854,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 1 because 2 + 5 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":991,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":22,"time_elapsed":1479845,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"instructions":"Now we're going to discuss a couple special properties of this new operation, +<sub>6</sub> that we've learned. First, notice that the number 0 behaves in a special way under +<sub>6</sub>. Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back. We'll say that 0 is the <i>identity</i> under +<sub>6</sub>, because when you combine it with something it gives you that identical thing back.","rt":10990,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":23,"time_elapsed":1490837,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now that we know 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>, we're going to make a new definition. We'll say that the <i>inverse</i> of a number is the element that you combine with it to produce the identity. For example, 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0, so we say 1 is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>6</sub>, (remember 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>). Similarly, 3 is its own inverse under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0.","rt":47008,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":24,"time_elapsed":1537846,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! What is the inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":60638,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":25,"time_elapsed":1598485,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub> is 2 because 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":10967,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":26,"time_elapsed":1609453,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":6206,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":27,"time_elapsed":1615661,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> is 5 because 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1175,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":28,"time_elapsed":1616837,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":2792,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":29,"time_elapsed":1619630,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub> is 3 because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1438,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":30,"time_elapsed":1621069,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":2729,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":31,"time_elapsed":1623798,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub> is 4 because 2 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":871,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":32,"time_elapsed":1624670,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"6","response_history":[" ","6"],"rt":14326,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":33,"time_elapsed":1638997,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub> is 0 because 0 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":3742,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":34,"time_elapsed":1642741,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"instructions":"It is also possible to successively apply +<sub>6</sub>, and the operation can simply be performed starting with the left-most pair. For example, 2 +<sub>6</sub> 3 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 3.","rt":8704,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":35,"time_elapsed":1651446,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"We have one last definition to learn today, using the successive operations we just learned. Let's start with an example. Under our operation +<sub>6</sub> we can make every other number using just 1: 2 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 3 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 4 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 5 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, and 0 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1. Because 1 can make every other element under +<sub>6</sub>, we sa y that 1  is a <i>generator</i> under +<sub>6</sub>. <br /><br /> However, 2 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, and 0 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 2.","rt":18510,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":36,"time_elapsed":1669957,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! Is 3 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":11904,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":37,"time_elapsed":1681862,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 = 3, 0 = 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, or 5 using just 3.","rt":6638,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":38,"time_elapsed":1688501,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":9928,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":39,"time_elapsed":1698430,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 5 is a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 5 = 5, 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 3 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 2 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 1 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, and 0 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, so you can make all of the numbers under +<sub>6</sub> using 5","rt":9279,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":40,"time_elapsed":1707709,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 4 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["Yes","No"],"rt":7721,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":41,"time_elapsed":1715431,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 4, 2 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, and 0 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 4.","rt":6559,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":42,"time_elapsed":1721991,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 0 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":[" No"],"rt":4000,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":43,"time_elapsed":1725991,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 0 = 0, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5 using just 0.","rt":2351,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":44,"time_elapsed":1728343,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"instructions":"Now we are going to ask you some questions about a new operation, +<sub>9</sub>, on the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. It works exactly like +<sub>6</sub>, except now after adding the two numbers you subtract 9 if your result is 9 or greater. <br /><br />Do you see how +<sub>9</sub> works just like +<sub>6</sub>? By subtracting 9 every time we get above 8, we ensure that when we combine two numbers using +<sub>9</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 8.<br /><br />We'll give you one practice question with feedback to make sure you understand the new oper ation. A fter that, try to complete the remaining questions as accurately as possible.","rt":12399,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":45,"time_elapsed":1740743,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Practice: What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":8951,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":46,"time_elapsed":1749695,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5 = 1 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 9 = 1.","rt":1406,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":47,"time_elapsed":1751102,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>9</sub> 3?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":3592,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":48,"time_elapsed":1754695,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"W hat is 7 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":5494,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":49,"time_elapsed":1760190,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>9</sub> 8?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":11406,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":50,"time_elapsed":1771597,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":5840,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":51,"time_elapsed":1777438,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 6 +<sub>9</sub> 6?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":3438,"trial_type":"que stion","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":52,"time_elapsed":1780878,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>9</sub> 1? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"5, because 4 plus 1 is 5, and 5 is less than 9","response_history":["5, because 4 plus 1 is 5, and 5 is less thannin","5, because 4 plus 1 is 5, and 5 is less thanni","5, because 4 plus 1 is 5, and 5 is less thann","5, because 4 plus 1 is 5, and 5 is less than 9"],"rt":35103,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":53,"time_elapsed":1815981,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 8 +<sub>9</sub> 4? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"3, because 8 plus 4 is 12, which is over 9, so we subtract 9 from 12, leaving 3","response_history":["3, because 8 plus 4 is 12, which is over 9, so we su btract 9  from 12, leaving 3"],"rt":32856,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":54,"time_elapsed":1848838,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the identity under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0 because 9 plus zero is nine, and then we subtract nine from that, leaving zero.","response_history":["0 because 9 plus zero is nine, and then we subtract nine from that, leaving zero."],"rt":117535,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":55,"time_elapsed":1966374,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":16238,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":56,"time_elapsed":1982613,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of  2 under  +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"7","response":"7","response_history":["7"],"rt":4225,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":57,"time_elapsed":1986839,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"9","response_history":["9"],"rt":5117,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":58,"time_elapsed":1991957,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"6 because 6 plus 3 is nine, and subtracting 9 from that leaves 0","response_history":["6 because 3","6 because 6 plus 3 is nine, and subtract ","6 because 6 plus 3 is nine, and subtracting 9 l","6 because 6 plus 3 is nine, and subtracting 9 from that  leaves  0"],"rt":30815,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":59,"time_elapsed":2022773,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 2 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I don't think so, because it wouldn't make every number below 9","response_history":["I don't think so, becuase ","I don't think so, becuase","I don't think so, becuas","I don't think so, becua","I don't think so, becu","I don't think so, because it wouldn't make every number below 9"],"rt":66472,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":60,"time_elapsed":2089246,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 3 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I don't think so, but I am unclear on the generator concept","response_history":["I do n't think so, but I am unclear on the generater","I don't think so, but I am unclear on the generate","I don't think so, but I am unclear on the generator concept"],"rt":28158,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":61,"time_elapsed":2117405,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I don't think so but I am not sure why","response_history":["I don't think so but I am not sure why"],"rt":18255,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":62,"time_elapsed":2135662,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 6 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I don't think so but I can't explain why","response_history":["I don't think so but I can't explain wh y"],"rt":11942,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":63,"time_elapsed":2147605,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"instructions":"Now we'd like to ask you some questions about +<sub>n</sub>, where n could be any postive counting number. For example, n could be 3, or n could be any other counting number you can think of. If you need to write the operation, you can use +_n, and your answers can include n to stand in for the arbitrary value if necessary.","rt":6984,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":64,"time_elapsed":2154590,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of 1 under +<sub>n</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-1","response":"I don't know","response_history":["I dont'","I dont","I don't know"],"rt":32166,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":65,"time_elapsed":2186757,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is the formu la for t he inverse of an element x under +<sub>n</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-x","response":"I am not sure, n plus n but I don't think so","response_history":["I am not sure, n plus n but I don't think so"],"rt":36607,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":66,"time_elapsed":2223365,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Is there a pattern to which elements are generators? How can you know if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub> without seeing whether it can make all the elements?.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"That's a good question, and I wish I could answer it","response_history":["That's a good question, and I wish I could answer it"],"rt":25503,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":67,"time_elapsed":2248869,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is a n odd nu mber, it must be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":19531,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":68,"time_elapsed":2268401,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an even number, it must not be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":10033,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":69,"time_elapsed":2278435,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a divisor of n, that is, x must divide n evenly, with no remainder.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","response_history":["True"],"rt":16321,"trial_type":"quest ion","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":70,"time_elapsed":2294757,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a multiple of a divisor of n. Please explain in words why your answer is correct.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"True","response":"I don't think I can explain this","response_history":["I am","I a","I don't think I can explain this"],"rt":33831,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":71,"time_elapsed":2328589,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is its inverse a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Always","response":"Never","response_history":["Never"],"rt":33495,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":72,"time_elapsed":2362085,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0. 14-0"},{"question":"if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never? Please explain in words why your answer is correct.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"sometimes","response":"sometimes, but the concept behind it is unclear to me","response_history":["sometimes, but the concept behind it is fuzzy","sometimes, but the concept behind it is fuzz","sometimes, but the concept behind it is fuz","sometimes, but the concept behind it is fu","sometimes, but the concept behind it is f","sometimes, but the concept behind it is unclear to me"],"rt":44448,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":73,"time_elapsed":2406534,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Alway s","Some times","Never"],"correct_response":"Never","response":"Sometimes","response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":23305,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":74,"time_elapsed":2429840,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"instructions":"We would like to ask you some questions about your background. Please press Continue to continue.","rt":1763,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":75,"time_elapsed":2431604,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your age?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"43","response_history":["43"],"rt":3063,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":76,"time_elapsed":2434667,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your level of education?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Did not graduate high school","High school diploma","Some college, no degree","Associates Degree","Bachelors Degree","Some graduate school, no de gree","M asters Degree","Doctorate, M.D., etc."],"correct_response":"","response":"Some college, no degree","response_history":["Some college, no degree"],"rt":2849,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":77,"time_elapsed":2437517,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is the most advanced math class you've completed? If you have multiple classes and you're not sure which one is most advanced, please list them.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"College Algebra, one class, about 20 years ago","response_history":["College Algebra, one class, about 20 years ago"],"rt":28567,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":78,"time_elapsed":2466085,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of modular arithmetic?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4  - used  it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","response_history":["2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was"],"rt":7421,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":79,"time_elapsed":2473507,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of a mathematical group?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":8101,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":80,"time_elapsed":2481609,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you learned something from this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1  - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":6421,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":81,"time_elapsed":2488031,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you understood the concepts in this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":3386,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":82,"time_elapsed":2491418,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you enjoy this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"3 - definitely","response_history":["3 - definitely"],"rt":4587,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":83,"time_elapsed":2496007,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your gender?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Female","Male","Other"],"correct_response":"","response":"Female","response_history":["Female"],"rt":4599,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":84,"time_elapsed":2500606,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is/are your native language(s)? (The languages spoken in your household when you were a child.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"English","response_history":["English"],"rt":4279,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":85,"time_elapsed":2504886,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you use pen and paper at any point on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Yes, but only to take a couple notes at the beginning","response_history":["Yes, but only to take a couple notes at the beginning"],"rt":23599,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":86,"time_elapsed":2528486,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you have any comments on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"This was interesting! I think if I would have taken some notes, I would have grasped the generator and inverse concepts much better.","response_history":["This was interesting! I think if I would have taken a not","This was interesting! I think if I would have taken a no","This was interesting! I think if I would have taken a n","This was interesting! I think if I would have taken a ","This was interesting! I think if I would have taken a","This was interesting! I think if I would have taken some notes, I would b","This was interesting! I think if I would have taken some notes, I would have grasped the generator and inverse concepts much better."],"rt":61135,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":87,"time_elapsed":2589622,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"}]